<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Categories on Charlie Thao</title><link>https://whatisthaodoing.today/categories/</link><description>Recent content in Categories</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>Page(/categories)</managingEditor><atom:link href="/categories/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My first journey with hotfix of Vietnamese flag on Xtranslation chap.1</title><link>https://whatisthaodoing.today/post/my-first-journey-with-hotfix-of-vietnamese-flag-on-xtranslation-chap.1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whatisthaodoing.today/post/my-first-journey-with-hotfix-of-vietnamese-flag-on-xtranslation-chap.1/</guid><description>How - When I found the hotfix By chance, I attempted to use a browser with translation when I encountered an unknown word. My friend suggested a reliable tool, Xtranslation. Upon use, I noticed that the flag of the Vietnamese language was different from the usual flag displayed.
Upon zooming in, I realized that the flag belonged to an island.
I then searched for the image on Google to determine which country or location the flag belonged to.</description></item><item><title>My first hacking challenge: SQL Injection chap.1</title><link>https://whatisthaodoing.today/post/my-first-hacking-challenge-sql-injection-chap.1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whatisthaodoing.today/post/my-first-hacking-challenge-sql-injection-chap.1/</guid><description>For first-time hackers, TryHackMe&amp;rsquo;s SQL Injection challenge can be both exciting and intimidating. Participants are tested on their ability to identify and exploit SQL vulnerabilities in the first task, while learning about common attack methods and preventative measures. Successfully completing the challenge builds confidence and prepares participants for future cybersecurity challenges. It&amp;rsquo;s a valuable learning experience for anyone interested in cybersecurity.</description></item><item><title>My first hacking challenge: SQL Injection chap.1</title><link>https://whatisthaodoing.today/post/my-first-hacking-challenge-sql-injection-chap.1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whatisthaodoing.today/post/my-first-hacking-challenge-sql-injection-chap.1/</guid><description>I have always been intrigued by the field of cybersecurity, and recently a friend recommended tryhackme.com to me. Eager to explore the world of hacking, I decided to take on my first challenge involving SQL Injection.
To my surprise, the experience was exhilarating and more stimulating than I had anticipated. I was completely engrossed in the task, eager to learn and solve more challenges.
Starting with the easier level, I can confidently say that my experience thus far has been nothing short of thrilling.</description></item><item><title>My first application: Weather forecast</title><link>https://whatisthaodoing.today/post/my-first-application-weather-forecast/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whatisthaodoing.today/post/my-first-application-weather-forecast/</guid><description>Web app to check weather forecast at a certain location</description></item></channel></rss>