<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>My first journey with hotfix on Charlie Thao</title><link>https://whatisthaodoing.today/tags/my-first-journey-with-hotfix/</link><description>Recent content in My first journey with hotfix</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>Page(/tags/my-first-journey-with-hotfix)</managingEditor><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/my-first-journey-with-hotfix/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My first journey with hotfix of Vietnamese flag on Xtranslation chap.1</title><link>https://whatisthaodoing.today/post/my-first-journey-with-hotfix-of-vietnamese-flag-on-xtranslation-chap.1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whatisthaodoing.today/post/my-first-journey-with-hotfix-of-vietnamese-flag-on-xtranslation-chap.1/</guid><description>Hotfix contribution to Xtranslation</description></item><item><title>My 1st application 'Weather forecast' CHAP.3: Configuration of Swagger and Adding MIT License</title><link>https://whatisthaodoing.today/post/my-1st-application-weather-forecast-chap.3-configuration-of-swagger-and-adding-mit-license/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whatisthaodoing.today/post/my-1st-application-weather-forecast-chap.3-configuration-of-swagger-and-adding-mit-license/</guid><description>In the third stage, Swagger was set up for RESTful web services development, while in the fourth stage, the permissive MIT license was added to the project. The Swagger configuration included custom information about the API, such as name, version, author, and license, and the MIT license specified the conditions for use, distribution, and modification of the code without significant legal restrictions.</description></item><item><title>My first application: Weather forecast CHAP.2</title><link>https://whatisthaodoing.today/post/my-first-application-weather-forecast-chap.2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whatisthaodoing.today/post/my-first-application-weather-forecast-chap.2/</guid><description>To develop the weather forecast application&amp;rsquo;s backend, dependencies were installed, including essential libraries and frameworks. The fundamental components, such as the WeatherForecast model, controller, and database repository, were then created, with a MemoryDatabase used for optimal performance. The backend was efficiently configured and operational.</description></item><item><title>My first hacking challenge: SQL Injection chap.2</title><link>https://whatisthaodoing.today/post/my-first-hacking-challenge-sql-injection-chap.2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whatisthaodoing.today/post/my-first-hacking-challenge-sql-injection-chap.2/</guid><description>In the second task, participants will work with an input box string, while the third task focuses on URL Injection. These challenges are designed to test the knowledge and problem-solving abilities in various cybersecurity scenarios. By completing these challenges, participants can gain valuable experience and insights into how to identify and mitigate security risks in real-world situations.</description></item><item><title>My first hacking challenge: SQL Injection chap.1</title><link>https://whatisthaodoing.today/post/my-first-hacking-challenge-sql-injection-chap.1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whatisthaodoing.today/post/my-first-hacking-challenge-sql-injection-chap.1/</guid><description>For first-time hackers, TryHackMe&amp;rsquo;s SQL Injection challenge can be both exciting and intimidating. Participants are tested on their ability to identify and exploit SQL vulnerabilities in the first task, while learning about common attack methods and preventative measures. Successfully completing the challenge builds confidence and prepares participants for future cybersecurity challenges. It&amp;rsquo;s a valuable learning experience for anyone interested in cybersecurity.</description></item><item><title>My first application: Weather forecast</title><link>https://whatisthaodoing.today/post/my-first-application-weather-forecast/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whatisthaodoing.today/post/my-first-application-weather-forecast/</guid><description>Web app to check weather forecast at a certain location</description></item><item><title>My first application: Weather forecast CHAP.1</title><link>https://whatisthaodoing.today/post/my-first-application-weather-forecast-chap.1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whatisthaodoing.today/post/my-first-application-weather-forecast-chap.1/</guid><description>The creation process of this weather forecast application began with initializing a project. This involved creating a Spring Boot application that provided a robust framework for developing a RESTful API. After setting up the project, the next step was to check the status of the API, which confirmed that the application was operational and ready for use. This meticulous and systematic approach to development ensured that the application was functional and responsive, allowing users to obtain up-to-date and accurate weather information at any given time.</description></item><item><title>Why using Spring Boot for my first application</title><link>https://whatisthaodoing.today/post/why-using-spring-boot-for-my-first-application/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whatisthaodoing.today/post/why-using-spring-boot-for-my-first-application/</guid><description>Beginning with numerous questions about the benefits of utilizing Spring Boot, I embarked on a journey to further comprehend the extensive and multifaceted capabilities of this versatile framework.</description></item></channel></rss>